When you hear the word 'carnivore', do you think of lions and bears and sharks, or humans?
当你听到"肉食动物"这个词时，你会想到狮子、熊和鲨鱼，还是人类？
Steak for breakfast, chicken breasts for lunch and salmon and lamb for dinner.
早餐吃牛排，午餐吃鸡胸肉，晚餐吃三文鱼和羊肉。
No veg and no carbs.
没有蔬菜，没有碳水化合物。
This is just a typical day for someone on the carnivore diet.
这只是遵循肉食饮食的人典型的一天。
It's a meal plan that only allows meat, poultry, eggs, fish, seafood, dairy products and water.
这是一种只允许吃肉、家禽、鸡蛋、鱼、海鲜、乳制品和水的饮食计划。
It's animal-based opposed to plant-based.
它以动物为基础，而不是以植物为基础。
But why are some people following this diet?
但为什么有些人会遵循这种饮食？
And what do nutritionists think about it?
营养学家对此又有什么看法呢？
The carnivore diet is a type of ketogenic diet.
肉食饮食是生酮饮食的一种。
Normally the body uses glucose from carbohydrates as energy, but when there's a lack of this, the liver breaks fat down into ketones.
通常，身体使用来自碳水化合物的葡萄糖作为能量，但当缺乏葡萄糖时，肝脏会将脂肪分解为酮体。
This essentially means the body can fuel itself using fat instead of sugar.
这本质上意味着身体可以使用脂肪而不是糖来为自己提供能量。
Followers of the diet may experience weight loss, especially early on.
遵循这种饮食的人可能会经历体重下降，尤其是在早期。
One reason for this is that protein is highly satiating, so you consume fewer calories.
其中一个原因是蛋白质具有很强的饱腹感，因此你摄入的卡路里更少。
On top of this, cutting out sugary snacks and fizzy drinks has significant health benefits, and when our carb intake is reduced, our stored water levels fall, again helping to reduce weight.
除此之外，戒掉含糖零食和碳酸饮料对健康有显著益处，当我们减少碳水化合物摄入时，体内储存的水分会下降，这也再次有助于减轻体重。
Nevertheless, the carnivore diet can't be described as 'balanced' by any stretch, according to health experts.
然而，健康专家表示，肉食饮食无论如何都不能被描述为"均衡"。
In fact, the British Heart Foundation strongly opposes it, saying there is no scientific evidence that it helps weight loss in the long term, and it's lacking in essential nutrients.
事实上，英国心脏基金会强烈反对这种饮食，称没有科学证据表明它有助于长期减肥，而且它缺乏必需的营养物质。
They say extreme diets which are low in fibre and high in fat can increase the risk of heart attacks and strokes.
他们说，纤维含量低、脂肪含量高的极端饮食会增加心脏病发作和中风的风险。
Saturated fat increases levels of LDL cholesterol and processed meat is high in salt which can raise blood pressure.
饱和脂肪会增加低密度脂蛋白胆固醇水平，而加工肉类的盐含量很高，会升高血压。
Fibre, they say, is necessary and counteracts all these issues, but it can only be found in 'banned foods' of the carnivore diet – fruits, vegetables, seeds, legumes and wholegrains, for example.
他们说，纤维是必需的，可以抵消所有这些问题，但纤维只存在于肉食饮食的"被禁止食用的食物"中——例如水果、蔬菜、种子、豆类和全谷物。
On social media you'll find plenty of people showing off their muscles and claiming their brain is working better than ever after weeks of fat and eggs and butter.
在社交媒体上，你会发现很多人炫耀自己的肌肉，并声称在几周只吃脂肪、鸡蛋和黄油后，他们的大脑比以往任何时候都工作得更好。
Influencer Paul Saladino was an advocate of the carnivore diet until he started experiencing some persistent unpleasant symptoms.
网红保罗·萨拉迪诺曾经是肉食饮食的倡导者，直到他开始出现一些持续不适的症状。
Speaking on a health and fitness podcast, he recounted heart palpitations, muscle cramps and sleep disturbances.
在一个健康健身播客中，他讲述了自己出现心悸、肌肉痉挛和睡眠障碍的经历。
He researched the diet more and concluded it was detrimental to his health and probably "not a great thing for most humans".
他进一步研究了这种饮食，并得出结论认为它对健康有害，而且可能"对大多数人来说不是一件好事"。
Most experts recommend balance, such as the Mediterranean diet, which is full of fruits, vegetables, wholegrains and seeds – it even includes meat, fish and eggs – but everything in moderation.
大多数专家建议均衡饮食，例如地中海饮食，它富含水果、蔬菜、全谷物和种子——它甚至包括肉、鱼和鸡蛋——但一切都需适度。